<?xml version="1.0"?>
<WorkshopItemInfo xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <PublishedFileId>2887840263</PublishedFileId>
  <Name>More Tech</Name>
  <Description>Adds some more tech to (late) game.
New Habs:
[list]
[*]Early tier-1 research lab providing 15 research
[*]More powerful fusion generator that uses exotic matter and antimatter to produce vast amounts of power, which is good as the other modules require a lot of power.
[*]More powerful solar farm that uses exotic matter and antimatter to produce vast amounts of power.
[*]Exotic matter production: uses antimatter and a lot of power to generate exotic matter &lt;*!* - note see below&gt;
[*]More Antimatter production: upgrades of the supercollider, using exotic matter for even more antimatter production
[*]Synthesiser: A matter-energy converter that generates basic resources for a hab
[*]Metal Irradiator: Turns metals and noble metals into fissible
[*]Six advanced Mining-Habs (two per tier)  that consume exotics and/or antimatter for increased yield
[*]An advanced Nanofactoring complex using exotic matter to produce more money an improve buildtime
[/list]

Projects
[list]
[*]Future-Tech: Welfare providing increased welfare reduction of global warming.
[*]Repeatable faction project: Advanced Space Exploitation Studies (5% Space Mining boost)
[*]Two projects reducing hab bombing damage
[*]Two projects reducing MCU signature for alien hate without Pherocryte Analysis
[*]Repeatable project to update the alien threat meter
[*]Repeatable project to extend councillors life expectancy
[/list]

Ship-Equipment
[list]
[*]Advanced plasma cannons (MKIV + MKV)
[*]Advanced Hybrid Armor
[/list]

(*)The exotics production means you will end up outproducing the aliens in this. To counteract this you can use [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3165648550] More Exotics for Aliens [/url] to boost their production as well.

For a change in balance regarding the vanilla buildings you can check out [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2888192881] Scale Up[/url]</Description>
  <IconFileName>More Tech.png</IconFileName>
  <Tags />
</WorkshopItemInfo>